Guide to the Office of Public Affairs, Yale University, Photographs of Individuals
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
- Photographs of Individuals, 1870-1972; Series I
  - Magowan, Stephen (Box 49, Folder 2209)
  - Maquire, John (Box 49, Folder 2210)
  - Mah, Francis (Box 49, Folder 2211)
  - Mahl, George F. (Box 49, Folder 2212)
  - Mahoney, Daniel (Box 49, Folder 2213)
  - Mailer, Norman (Box 49, Folder 2214)
  - Malik, Charles H. (Box 49, Folder 2215)
  - Malik, Fazley Bary (Box 49, Folder 2216)
  - Malinowski, Bronislaw (Box 49, Folder 2217)
  - Maliszewski, Stas (Box 49, Folder 2218)
  - Malkin, Myron S. (Box 49, Folder 2219)
  - Mallon, Henry Neil (Box 49, Folder 2220)
  - Mallory, William N. (Box 49, Folder 2221)
  - Malone, ----- (Box 49, Folder 2222)
  - Maltby, Richard E., Jr. (Box 49, Folder 2223)
  - Manners, Roger (Box 49, Folder 2224)
  - Manning, Bayless A. (Box 49, Folder 2225)
  - Mansbridge, Ronald (Box 49, Folder 2226)
  - Mantel, Ana M. & Rolf R. (Box 49, Folder 2227)
  - Manuelidis, Elias E. (Box 49, Folder 2228)
  - Marat-Sade (Box 49, Folder 2229)
  - March, Frederick (Box 49, Folder 2230)
  - Marchesi, Vincent T. (Box 49, Folder 2231)
  - Marchi, ----- (Box 49, Folder 2232)
  - Marcus, Edward (Box 49, Folder 2233)
  - Marcus, Leonard J. (Box 49, Folder 2234)
  - Marcuse, Herbert (Box 49, Folder 2235)
  - Margenau, Henry (Box 49, Folder 2236)
  - Markert, Clement L. (Box 49, Folder 2237-38)
  - Marland, ----- (Box 49, Folder 2239)
  - Marsh, Ronald C. (Box 49, Folder 2240)
  - Marshak, Jacob (Box 49, Folder 2241)
  - Marshall, Burke (Box 49, Folder 2242)
  - Marshall, Thurgood (Box 49, Folder 2243)
  - Marston, Thomas E. (Box 50, Folder 2244)
  - Martin, Alexander R. (Box 50, Folder 2245)
  - Martin, David B. H. (Box 50, Folder 2246)
  - Martin, Jay H. (Box 50, Folder 2247)
  - Martn, Joseph W. (Box 50, Folder 2248)
  - Martin, Samuel E. (Box 50, Folder 2249)
  - Martin, William McChesney (Box 50, Folder 2250)
  - Martino, Donald J. (Box 50, Folder 2251)
  - Martz, Louis L. (Box 50, Folder 2252)
  - Marvin, Harold M. (Box 50, Folder 2253)
  - Mass, James W. (Box 50, Folder 2254)
  - Massey, William S. (Box 50, Folder 2255)
  - Masters, Irene (Box 50, Folder 2256)
  - Master, Roger D. (Box 50, Folder 2257)
  - Mastrangelo, Jerry (Box 50, Folder 2258)
  - Mathewson, Champion H. (Box 50, Folder 2259)
  - Mathias, Charles (Box 50, Folder 2260)
  - Matson, Theodore (Box 50, Folder 2261)
  - Matter, Herbert (Box 50, Folder 2262)
  - Mau, James A. (Box 50, Folder 2263)
  - Mauceri, J. (Box 50, Folder 2264)
  - Maugham, W. Somerset (Box 50, Folder 2265)
  - Maun, Henry B. (Box 50, Folder 2266)
  - Maun, J. Robert, Jr. (Box 50, Folder 2267)
  - Maunder, Elwood R. (Box 50, Folder 2268)
  - Mautner, Henry G. (Box 50, Folder 2269)
  - May, Georges (Box 50, Folder 2270)
  - May, John D. (Box 50, Folder 2272)
  - May, Katherine (Box 50, Folder 2273)
  - May, Mark A. (Box 50, Folder 2274)
  - Mayers, Martin A. (Box 50, Folder 2275)
  - Mayr, Ernst (Box 50, Folder 2276)
  - McAlester, A. Lee (Box 50, Folder 2277)
  - McAlester, ----- (Box 50, Folder 2278)
  - McBride, William (Box 50, Folder 2279)
  - McCabe, Arthur E. (Box 50, Folder 2280)
  - McCaffrey, ----- (Box 50, Folder 2281)
  - McCandless, Hugh (Box 50, Folder 2282)
  - McCandless, Stanley (Box 50, Folder 2283)
  - McCarthy, ----- (Box 50, Folder 2284)
  - McCarthy, Charles (Box 50, Folder 2285)
  - McCarthy, Charles E., Jr. (Box 50, Folder 2286)
  - McCarthy, Eugene (Box 50, Folder 2287)
  - McCarthy, Raymond G. (Box 50, Folder 2288)
  - McClellan, Anthony R. (Box 50, Folder 2289)
  - McClellan, Edwin (Box 50, Folder 22890)
  - McClusky, Audrey M. (Box 50, Folder 2291)
  - McCollum, Robert W. (Box 51, Folder 2292)
  - McColough, C. Peter (Box 51, Folder 2293)
  - McConnell, Hugh (Box 51, Folder 2294)
  - McConoughy, James L. (Box 51, Folder 2295)
  - McCord, James I. (Box 51, Folder 2296)
  - McCormick, James C. (Box 51, Folder 2297)
  - McCormick, Vance (Box 51, Folder 2298)
  - McCoy, Rhody (Box 51, Folder 2299)
  - McCurdy, Charles J. (Box 51, Folder 2300)
  - McDoo, Charles (Box 51, Folder 2301)
  - McDougal, Myers S. (Box 51, Folder 2302)
  - McDowell, Dean N. (Box 51, Folder 2303)
  - McFeeley, William S., Jr. (Box 51, Folder 2304)
  - McGill, Ralph (Box 51, Folder 2305)
  - McGlaughin, ----- (Box 51, Folder 2306)
  - McGovern, George (Box 51, Folder 2307)
  - McGowan, John J. (Box 51, Folder 2308)
  - McGrillis, John O. C. (Box 51, Folder 2309)
  - McIntosh, James H. (Box 51, Folder 2310)
  - McIntosh, Millicent (Box 51, Folder 2311)
  - McKee, Elmore M. (Box 51, Folder 2312)
  - McKeehan, Louis W. (Box 51, Folder 2313)
  - McKeldin, ----- (Box 51, Folder 2314)
  - McKelway, St. Clair (Box 51, Folder 2315)
  - McKnight, Douglas (Box 51, Folder 2316)
  - McKnight, Everett J. (Box 51, Folder 2317)
  - McLaughlin, Edward (Box 51, Folder 2318)
  - McLaughry, John J. (Box 51, Folder 2319)
  - McLean, ----- (Box 51, Folder 2320)
  - McMahon, Joseph H. (Box 51, Folder 2321)
  - McMartin, William Jr. (Box 51, Folder 2322)
  - McMullan, Frank (Box 51, Folder 2323)
  - McManus, Francis (Box 51, Folder 2324)
  - McNamara, Francis T. (Box 51, Folder 2325)
  - McNamara, Robert S. (Box 51, Folder 2326)
  - McNeill, Malcolm D. O. (Box 51, Folder 2327)
  - McNerney, Jim (Box 51, Folder 2328)
  - McNerney, Robert F. (Box 51, Folder 2329)
  - McNerney, Walter J. (Box 51, Folder 2330)
  - McNulty, James M. (Box 51, Folder 2331)
  - Mead, Donald C. (Box 51, Folder 2332)
  - Mead, Margaret (Box 51, Folder 2333)
  - Medved, Mike (Box 51, Folder 2334)
  - Meeks, Carroll L. V. (Box 51, Folder 2335)
  - Meeks, Everett (Box 51, Folder 2336)
  - Meier, Gustav (Box 51, Folder 2337)
  - Meier, Richard A. (Box 51, Folder 2338)
  - Meigs, Josiah (Box 51, Folder 2339)
  - Meigs, Wister J. (Box 51, Folder 2340)
  - Meisel, John (Box 51, Folder 2341)
  - Mellon, Paul (Box 52, Folder 2342)
  - Mellon, Stanley I. (Box 52, Folder 2343)
  - Melman, Seymour (Box 52, Folder 2344)
  - Melnick, Joseph L. (Box 52, Folder 2345)
  - Mendel, Lafayette B. (Box 52, Folder 2346)
  - Mendell, Clarence W. (Box 52, Folder 2347)
  - Mendenhall, Thomas C. (Box 52, Folder 2348)
  - Menner, Robert J. (Box 52, Folder 2349)
  - Menocal, ----- (Editor, PARIS REVIEW ) (Box 52, Folder 2350)
  - Meredith, William (Box 52, Folder 2351)
  - Mergen, Francois (Box 52, Folder 2352)
  - Merlini, Charles (Box 52, Folder 2353)
  - Merrill, John W. (Box 52, Folder 2354)
  - Merriman, Daniel (Box 52, Folder 2355)
  - Merriss, Geoffrey (Box 52, Folder 2356)
  - Merritt, Alfred K. (Box 52, Folder 2357)
  - Meskill, Thomas (Box 52, Folder 2358)
  - Mesthene, Emmanuel (Box 52, Folder 2359)
  - Mettee, David R. (Box 52, Folder 2360)
  - Metz, Charles B. (Box 52, Folder 2361)
  - Metzdork, Robert F. (Box 52, Folder 2362)
  - Meyer, Eugene (Box 52, Folder 2363)
  - Meyer, John R. (Box 52, Folder 2364)
  - Meyer, Laurence (Box 52, Folder 2365)
  - Meyer, Paul W. (Box 52, Folder 2366)
  - Meyer, Russ (Box 52, Folder 2367)
  - Meyer, Walter H. (Box 52, Folder 2368)
  - Michaelson, Robert S. (Box 52, Folder 2369)
  - Michel, Lawrence A., Jr. (Box 52, Folder 2370)
  - Migdalski, Edward C. (Box 52, Folder 2371)
  - Mikasa, Prince (Box 52, Folder 2372)
  - Miles, Egbert J. (Box 52, Folder 2373)
  - Miles, James B. (Box 52, Folder 2374)
  - Miles, Walter R. (Box 52, Folder 2375)
  - Millbank, ----- (Box 52, Folder 2376)
  - Miller, Alfred B. (Box 52, Folder 2377)
  - Miller, Andrew (Box 52, Folder 2378)
  - Miller, Arthur (Box 52, Folder 2379)
  - Miller, Dudley P. (Box 52, Folder 2380)
  - Miller, Henry (Box 52, Folder 2381)
  - Miller, Hiriam Allen (Box 52, Folder 2382)
  - Miller, Irwin J. (Box 52, Folder 2383)
  - Miller, J. Hillis (Box 52, Folder 2384)
  - Miller, John A. (Box 53, Folder 2385)
  - Miller, John Perry (Box 53, Folder 2386)
  - Miller, Jonathon S. (Box 53, Folder 2387)
  - Miller, Joseph A. (Box 53, Folder 2388)
  - Miller, Mordecai (Box 53, Folder 2389)
  - Miller, Neal E. (Box 53, Folder 2390)
  - Miller, Ogden (Box 53, Folder 2391)
  - Miller, Randolph C. (Box 53, Folder 2392)
  - Miller, Richard (Box 53, Folder 2393)
  - Miller, Robbins H. (Box 53, Folder 2394)
  - Miller, Roy Andrew (Box 53, Folder 2395)
  - Miller, Spencer (Box 53, Folder 2396)
  - Miller, William Lee (Box 53, Folder 2397)
  - Milligan, William E. (Box 53, Folder 2398)
  - Millikan, James D. (Box 53, Folder 2399)
  - Milliken, George L. (Box 53, Folder 2400)
  - Milliken, Seth Minot (Box 53, Folder 2401)
  - Mills, John L. (Box 53, Folder 2402)
  - Mills, Stanley (Box 53, Folder 2403)
  - Mills, Theodore M. (Box 53, Folder 2404)
  - Milstone, Haskell J. (Box 53, Folder 2405)
  - Mims, John A. (Box 53, Folder 2406)
  - Mindell, Carl (Box 53, Folder 2407)
  - Minear, Paul S. (Box 53, Folder 2408)
  - Minter, David L. (Box 53, Folder 2409)
  - Mintz, Jacqueline Wei (Box 53, Folder 2410)
  - Mintz, Sidney W. (Box 53, Folder 2411)
  - Mintzner, David (Box 53, Folder 2412)
  - Miranda, Douglas (Box 53, Folder 2413)
  - Miskimin, Harry A., Jr. (Box 53, Folder 2414)
  - Mitchell, Donald G. (Box 53, Folder 2415)
  - Mitchell, Elisha (Box 53, Folder 2416)
  - Mitchell, James B. (Box 53, Folder 2417)
  - Mitchell, Stephen Mix (Box 53, Folder 2418)
  - Mittlefehldt, Victor (Box 53, Folder 2419)
  - Mixter, William G. (Box 53, Folder 2420)
  - Moerschbaecher, Lynda (Box 53, Folder 2421)
  - Moffett, Howard M. (Box 53, Folder 2422)
  - Mogenson, Arnold (Box 53, Folder 2423)
  - Moley, Raymond (Box 53, Folder 2424)
  - Moll, Richard W. (Box 53, Folder 2425)
  - Molotsi, Peter (Box 53, Folder 2426)
  - Montgomery, Carol G. (Box 53, Folder 2427)
  - Montgomery, Charles F. (Box 53, Folder 2428)
  - Mood, Eric W. (Box 53, Folder 2429)
  - Moore, Burness E. (Box 53, Folder 2430)
  - Moore, Charles (Box 53, Folder 2431)
  - Moore, Douglas (Box 53, Folder 2432)
  - Moore, Eliakin H. (Box 53, Folder 2433)
  - Moore, Frank G. (Box 53, Folder 2434)
  - Moore, James W. (Box 53, Folder 2435)
  - Moore, Lamont (Box 54, Folder 2436)
  - Moore, Maury K. (Box 54, Folder 2437)
  - Moore, Omar K. (Box 54, Folder 2438)
  - Moore, Paul, Jr. (Box 54, Folder 2439)
  - Moore, Pete (Box 54, Folder 2440)
  - Moore, Sally (Box 54, Folder 2441-42)
  - Morehouse, Andrew R. (Box 54, Folder 2443)
  - Morell, ----- (Box 54, Folder 2444)
  - Morgan, Charles (Box 54, Folder 2445)
  - Morgan, Edmund S. (Box 54, Folder 2446)
  - Morgan, Edward P. (Box 54, Folder 2447)
  - Morgan, Jim (Box 54, Folder 2448)
  - Morgan, John Hill (Box 54, Folder 2449)
  - Morgens, Howard J. (Box 54, Folder 2450)
  - Moriarty, Paul (Box 54, Folder 2451)
  - Moriarty, Philip E. (Box 54, Folder 2452-53)
  - Moriarty, Philip S. J. (Box 54, Folder 2454)
  - Morison, Elting E. (Box 54, Folder 2455)
  - Moritz, Paul R. (Box 54, Folder 2456)
  - Morowitz, Harold J. (Box 54, Folder 2457)
  - Morrill, Mrs. Ralph (Box 54, Folder 2458)
  - Morris, Edward P. (Box 54, Folder 2459)
  - Morris, James M. (Box 54, Folder 2460)
  - Morris, John McL. (Box 54, Folder 2461)
  - Morris, Luzon B. (Box 54, Folder 2462)
  - Morris, Newbald (Box 54, Folder 2463)
  - Morris, Percy A. (Box 54, Folder 2464)
  - Morris, Raymond P. (Box 54, Folder 2465)
  - Morrison, Jack (Box 54, Folder 2466)
  - Morrow, James E., Jr. (Box 54, Folder 2467)
  - Morrow, Samuel R. (Box 54, Folder 2468)
  - Morse, Charles J. (Box 54, Folder 2469)
  - Morse, Richard M. (Box 54, Folder 2470)
  - Morse, Samuel F. B. (Box 54, Folder 2471)
  - Morse, Wayne (Box 54, Folder 2472)
  - Morton, Francis Reiser (Box 54, Folder 2473)
  - Morton, Rogers C. B. (Box 54, Folder 2474)
  - Morton, Thurston (Box 54, Folder 2475)
  - Moscosl, Vic (Box 54, Folder 2476)
  - Moseley, Spencer D. (Box 54, Folder 2477)
  - Moser, Charles A. (Box 54, Folder 2478)
  - Moses, B. Hopkins (Box 54, Folder 2479)
  - Moses, R. (Box 54, Folder 2480)
  - Moses, Robert (Box 54, Folder 2481)
  - Moskowitz, Merwin (Box 54, Folder 2482)
  - Mosman, Warren T. (Box 54, Folder 2483)
  - Moss, Lawrence K. (Box 54, Folder 2484)
  - Mostow, George D. (Box 54, Folder 2485)
  - Moulton, James S. (Box 54, Folder 2486)
  - Mourelatus, Alexander P. D. (Box 54, Folder 2487)
  - Mowe, Homer G. (Box 54, Folder 2488)
  - Mowrer, O. Hobart (Box 54, Folder 2489)
  - Muehl, E. William (Box 54, Folder 2490)
  - Mueller, Addison A. (Box 54, Folder 2491)
  - Mueller, Mary (Box 54, Folder 2492)
  - Mueller, Michael J. (Box 55, Folder 2493)
  - Muir, William K., Jr. (Box 55, Folder 2494)
  - Mulder, Gerrit (Box 55, Folder 2495)
  - Muller, ----- (Box 55, Folder 2496)
  - Muller-Bergh, Klaus (Box 55, Folder 2497)
  - Mullestein, W. E. (Box 55, Folder 2498)
  - Mulrow, Patrick J., M.D. (Box 55, Folder 2499)
  - Mundt, Carl (Box 55, Folder 2500)
  - Munger, Theodore Thornton (Box 55, Folder 2501)
  - Munhall, Edgar J. (Box 55, Folder 2502)
  - Munson, Aeneas (Box 55, Folder 2503)
  - Murdock, George P. (Box 55, Folder 2504)
  - Murphy, George (Box 55, Folder 2505)
  - Murphy, John B. (Box 55, Folder 2506)
  - Murphy, Richard (Box 55, Folder 2507)
  - Murphy, Roland E. (Box 55, Folder 2508)
  - Murray, Geoffrey P. (Box 55, Folder 2509)
  - Murray, John C. (Box 55, Folder 2510)
  - Murray, Pauli (Box 55, Folder 2511)
  - Mus, Paul (Box 55, Folder 2512)
  - Musick, ----- (Box 55, Folder 2513)
  - Muskie, Edmund (Box 55, Folder 2514)
  - Musselman, Luther K. (Box 55, Folder 2515)
  - Musser, John M. (Box 55, Folder 2516)
  - Muyskens, John, Jr. (Box 55, Folder 2517)
  - Myers, Albert E. (Box 55, Folder 2518)
  - Myers, Jerome K. (Box 55, Folder 2519)
  - Mylon, Ernst (Box 55, Folder 2520)
  - Nader, Ralph (Box 55, Folder 2521)
  - Nagel, Charles (Box 55, Folder 2522)
  - Nagler, Alois (Box 55, Folder 2523)
  - Nahum, Louis H., M.D. (Box 55, Folder 2524)
  - Nanda, Ved (Box 55, Folder 2525)
  - Nangle, Benjamin C. & Mrs. (Box 55, Folder 2526)
  - Napier, B. Davie (Box 55, Folder 2527-28)
  - Narenda, Kumpati S. (Box 55, Folder 2529)
  - Nash, June (Box 55, Folder 2530)
  - Nash, Kermit B., Jr. (Box 55, Folder 2531)
  - Natunewicz, Chester (Box 55, Folder 2532)
  - Naylor, Aubrey W. (Box 55, Folder 2533-34)
  - Neale, William H. (Box 55, Folder 2535)
  - Needham, Wesley E. (Box 55, Folder 2536)
  - Neely, ----- (Box 55, Folder 2537)
  - Neill, Peter (Box 55, Folder 2538)
  - Nelson, C. William (Box 55, Folder 2539)
  - Nelson, Dorothy Ann (Box 55, Folder 2540)
  - Nelson, John Oliver (Box 56, Folder 2541)
  - Nelson, Lowry, Jr. (Box 56, Folder 2542)
  - Nelson, Philip F. (Box 56, Folder 2543)
  - Nelson, Richard R. (Box 56, Folder 2544)
  - Nelson, Robert A., Jr. (Box 56, Folder 2545)
  - Nelson, Thomas A. (Box 56, Folder 2546)
  - Nelson, William (Box 56, Folder 2547)
  - Nemoy, Leon (Box 56, Folder 2548)
  - Neri, Jerry (Box 56, Folder 2549)
  - Nerlove, Marc Leon (Box 56, Folder 2550)
  - Nesheim, Roberta (Box 56, Folder 2551)
  - Nettleton, George H. (Box 56, Folder 2552)
  - Neutra, Richard (Box 56, Folder 2553)
  - Newbigin, Lesslie (Box 56, Folder 2554)
  - Newell, Norman Dennis (Box 56, Folder 2555)
  - Newfield, Lou K., Jr. (Box 56, Folder 2556)
  - Newman, ----- (Box 56, Folder 2557)
  - Newman, Paul (Box 56, Folder 2558)
  - Newton, ----- (Box 56, Folder 2559)
  - Newton, Hubert (Box 56, Folder 2560)
  - Nicholas, John S. (Box 56, Folder 2561)
  - Nichols, Jan (Box 56, Folder 2562)
  - Nichols, William Wallace (Box 56, Folder 2563)
  - Nicklas, R. Bruce (Box 56, Folder 2564)
  - Nicoll, Allardyce (Box 56, Folder 2565)
  - Niebuhr, H. Richard (Box 56, Folder 2566)
  - Niemeyer, John Jenery (Box 56, Folder 2567)
  - Nikolaevsky, B. (Box 56, Folder 2568)
  - Nimetz, Michael G. (Box 56, Folder 2569)
  - Nivola, ----- (Stiles sculptor) (Box 56, Folder 2570)
  - Nixon, Richard (Box 56, Folder 2571)
  - Nizer, Louis (Box 56, Folder 2572)
  - Nkrumah, Kwame (Box 56, Folder 2573)
  - Noble, Dale (Box 56, Folder 2574)
  - Noble, Lawrence M., Jr. (Box 56, Folder 2575)
  - Noble, Thomas A. (Box 56, Folder 2576)
  - Nolan, William J. (Box 56, Folder 2577)
  - Nolen, George Augustus (Box 56, Folder 2578)
  - Nooney, James (Box 56, Folder 2579)
  - Norbert, (Sister) (Box 56, Folder 2580)
  - Nordhaus, William D. (Box 56, Folder 2581)
  - Nordmeyer, George (Box 56, Folder 2582)
  - North, Simon (Box 56, Folder 2583)
  - Northrop, Cyrus (Box 56, Folder 2584)
  - Northrop, Filmer (Box 56, Folder 2585)
  - Norton, John P. (Box 56, Folder 2586)
  - Norton, William A. (Box 56, Folder 2587)
  - Noss, Luther (Box 57, Folder 2588)
  - Notestein, (Ada Comstock) Mrs. Wallace (Box 57, Folder 2589)
  - Notestein, wallace (Box 57, Folder 2590)
  - Nouwen, Henri (Box 57, Folder 2591)
  - Nowak, Laurence (Box 57, Folder 2592)
  - Nowick, Arthur S. (Box 57, Folder 2593)
  - Noyce, Gaylord B. (Box 57, Folder 2594)
  - Noyes, Edward S. (Box 57, Folder 2595)
  - Noyes, Eliot F. (Box 57, Folder 2596)
  - Noyes, Morgan P. (Box 57, Folder 2597)
  - Nutter, G. Warren (Box 57, Folder 2598)
  - Nutting, Anthony (Box 57, Folder 2599)
  - Nyman, Richmond C. (Box 57, Folder 2600)
  - Oates, John F. (Box 57, Folder 2601)
  - Obelensky, R. M. (Box 57, Folder 2602)
  - Oberman, Julian J. (Box 57, Folder 2603)
  - O'Brien, ----- (Box 57, Folder 2604)
  - O'Connor, George E. (Box 57, Folder 2605)
  - O'Connor, John F. (Box 57, Folder 2606)
  - O'Connor, Robert E. (Box 57, Folder 2607)
  - O'Daniel, Orville K. (Box 57, Folder 2608)
  - Odell, Howie (Box 57, Folder 2609)
  - Oenslager, Donald M. (Box 57, Folder 2610)
  - Ogilvie, Donald G. (Box 57, Folder 2611)
  - Ogilvy, David M. (Box 57, Folder 2612)
  - O'Hearn, Charles M. (Box 57, Folder 2613)
  - Okobu (Box 57, Folder 2614)
  - Okun, Arthur M. (Box 57, Folder 2615)
  - Olds, Irving S. (Box 57, Folder 2616)
  - Olivar, Jordan (Box 57, Folder 2617)
  - Oliver, Alderman (Box 57, Folder 2618)
  - Olmstead, Denison (Box 57, Folder 2619)
  - Olmstead, Frederick Law (Box 57, Folder 2620)
  - Olson, Bernard E. (Box 57, Folder 2621)
  - Olson, Donald R. (Box 57, Folder 2622)
  - Omwake, Eveline B. (Box 57, Folder 2623)
  - Onat, Emin T. (Box 57, Folder 2624)
  - O'Neill, Eugene (Box 57, Folder 2625)
  - Onsager, Lars (Box 57, Folder 2626)
  - Oppenheimer, J. Robert (Box 57, Folder 2627)
  - Opsahl, Jeanette C. (Box 57, Folder 2628)
  - Orcutt, Guy (Box 58, Folder 2629)
  - Ordung, Philp F. (Box 58, Folder 2630)
  - Ordway, Nelson K. (Box 58, Folder 2631)
  - Ore, Oystein (Box 58, Folder 2632)
  - de Oris, Juan (Box 58, Folder 2633)
  - Ornston, Darius Gray, Jr. (M.D.) (Box 58, Folder 2634)
  - Orser, Frank W. (Box 58, Folder 2635)
  - Ortali, Ray (Box 58, Folder 2636)
  - Ortel, Hans (Box 58, Folder 2637)
  - Orville, Philip M. (Box 58, Folder 2638)
  - Osborn, James M. (Box 58, Folder 2639)
  - Osborn, Norris G. (Box 58, Folder 2640)
  - Osborne, Ernest L. (Box 58, Folder 2641)
  - Osborne, Thomas B. (Box 58, Folder 2642)
  - Osgood, Cornelius (Box 58, Folder 2643)
  - Oster, Ludwig (Box 58, Folder 2644)
  - Ostergren, Christopher (Box 58, Folder 2645)
  - Osterweis, Rollin G. (Box 58, Folder 2646)
  - Ostfeld, Adrian M. (Box 58, Folder 2647)
  - Ostrander, ----- (Box 58, Folder 2648)
  - Ostrom, John H. (Box 58, Folder 2649)
  - Otis, Charles P. (Box 58, Folder 2650)
  - Ottemiller, John H. (Box 58, Folder 2651)
  - Ottley, William H. (Box 58, Folder 2652)
  - Oughterson, Ashley W. (Box 58, Folder 2653)
  - Outler, Albert C. (Box 58, Folder 2654)
  - Owen, Benton B. (Box 58, Folder 2655)
  - Owen, John J. (Box 58, Folder 2656)
  - Owen, Stephen (Box 58, Folder 2657)
  - Owen, William H. (Box 58, Folder 2658)
  - Oxtoby, Willard G. (Box 58, Folder 2659)
  - Oystein, Ore (Box 58, Folder 2660)
  - P (unidentified) (Box 58, Folder 2661)
  - Pachachi, Odman (Box 58, Folder 2662)
  - Pacifici, Sergio H. (Box 58, Folder 2663)
  - Pack, George T. (Box 58, Folder 2664)
  - Pack, Howard (Box 58, Folder 2665)
  - Packard, Lewis R. (Box 58, Folder 2666)
  - Paige, Lee (Box 58, Folder 2667)
  - Paine, Ralph D., Jr. (Box 58, Folder 2668)
  - Palay, Sanford L. (Box 58, Folder 2669)
  - Paley, Barbara (Box 58, Folder 2670)
  - Palisca, Claude V. (Box 58, Folder 2671)
  - Palmer, Charles Ray (Box 58, Folder 2672)
  - Palmer, John J. EA. (Box 58, Folder 2673)
  - Palmer, Thomas W. (Box 58, Folder 2674)
  - Panetti, Joan C. (Box 58, Folder 2675)
  - Pap, Arthur (Box 58, Folder 2676)
  - Papazian, Haig P. (Box 58, Folder 2677)
  - Papke, David R. (Box 58, Folder 2678)
  - Papp, Joseph (Box 58, Folder 2679)
  - Pappenheim, Fritz (Box 58, Folder 2680)
  - Paquin, Lawrence (Box 58, Folder 2681)
  - Paradise, N. Burton (Box 58, Folder 2682)
  - Parker, Everett C. (Box 58, Folder 2683)
  - Parker, Fess (Box 59, Folder 2684)
  - Parker, Hank (Box 59, Folder 2685)
  - Parker, John (Box 59, Folder 2686)
  - Parker, W. Oren (Box 59, Folder 2687)
  - Parker, William N. (Box 59, Folder 2688)
  - Parkinson, ----- (Box 59, Folder 2689)
  - Parmen, ----- (Box 59, Folder 2690)
  - Paros, Larry (Box 59, Folder 2691)
  - Parr, Albert E. (Box 59, Folder 2692)
  - Parry, Adam (Box 59, Folder 2693)
  - Parsons, Francis (Box 59, Folder 2694)
  - Parsons, Lewis A. (Box 59, Folder 2695)
  - Passano, Leonard M. (Box 59, Folder 2696)
  - Partridge, Warine (Box 59, Folder 2697)
  - Patel, Jehangor (Box 59, Folder 2698)
  - Patrick, Hugh T. (Box 59, Folder 2699)
  - Patterson, Andrew (Box 59, Folder 2700)
  - Patton, William H. (Box 59, Folder 2701)
  - Paul, John R. (Box 59, Folder 2702)
  - Paul, Norman (Box 59, Folder 2703)
  - Paulson, David F. (Box 59, Folder 2704)
  - Payne, Anthony Monck-Mason, M.D. (Box 59, Folder 2705)
  - Peabody, Endicott and Mrs. Peabody (Box 59, Folder 2706)
  - Pearson, Norman Holmes (Box 59, Folder 2707)
  - Pearson, R. John C. (Box 59, Folder 2708)
  - Peberdy, Grafton (Box 59, Folder 2709)
  - Pechman, Joseph S. (Box 59, Folder 2710)
  - Peck, Merton J. (Box 59, Folder 2711)
  - Peck, Tracy (Box 59, Folder 2712)
  - Peel, Roger M. (Box 59, Folder 2713)
  - Peffer, Robert (Box 59, Folder 2714)
  - Pelczynski, Zbigniew A. (Box 59, Folder 2715)
  - Pelikan, Jaroslav J., Jr. (Box 59, Folder 2716)
  - Pellegrino, Edmund D. (Box 59, Folder 2717)
  - Pelli, Cesar (Box 59, Folder 2718)
  - Pelly, Thomas M. (Box 59, Folder 2719)
  - Pelzer, Karl J. (Box 59, Folder 2720)
  - Pendleton, Austin (Box 59, Folder 2721)
  - Pendleton, Claudius V. (Box 59, Folder 2722)
  - Penfield, Samuel L. (Box 59, Folder 2723)
  - Penfield, Wilder (Box 59, Folder 2724)
  - Penny, Sharon H. (Box 59, Folder 2725)
  - Pepper, Max P. (Box 59, Folder 2726)
  - Peraez, ----- (Box 59, Folder 2727)
  - Percival, James G. (Box 59, Folder 2728)
  - Perelman, S. J. (Box 59, Folder 2729)
  - Pergam, Al (Box 59, Folder 2730)
  - Perkins, Frederick P. (Box 59, Folder 2731)
  - Perkins, Henrietta T. (Box 59, Folder 2732)
  - Perkins, Leeman L. (Box 59, Folder 2733)
  - Perkins, William (Box 59, Folder 2734)
  - Perlis, Alan J. (Box 59, Folder 2735)
  - Perrin, Bernadotte (Box 59, Folder 2736)
  - Perry, George W. (Box 60, Folder 2737)
  - Peterdi, Gabor F. (Box 60, Folder 2738)
  - Peterkin, De Witt, Jr. (Box 60, Folder 2739)
  - Peters, Charles Adams (Box 60, Folder 2740)
  - Peters, Ellen A. (Box 60, Folder 2741)
  - Peters, John H. (Box 60, Folder 2742)
  - Peters, Robert H. (Box 60, Folder 2743)
  - Peterson, ----- (Box 60, Folder 2744)
  - Peterson, Douglas W. (Box 60, Folder 2745)
  - Peterson, ervin L. (Box 60, Folder 2746)
  - Peterson, marvin K. (Box 60, Folder 2747)
  - Peterson, Stephen L. (Box 60, Folder 2748)
  - Petrov, Vladimir (Box 60, Folder 2749)
  - Petrunkevitch, Alexander (Box 60, Folder 2750)
  - Peyre, Henri (Box 60, Folder 2751)
  - Peyton, John (Box 60, Folder 2752)
  - Pfeffer, Ronald F. (Box 60, Folder 2753)
  - Pfisterer, Henry A. (Box 60, Folder 2754)
  - Phelan, Howard T. (Box 60, Folder 2755)
  - Phelps, Ashton (Box 60, Folder 2756)
  - Phelps, Edward J. (Box 60, Folder 2757)
  - Phelps, John B. (Box 60, Folder 2758)